(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
oath sign 作詞・作曲 渡辺翔
oath sign Lyrics & Composition by Sho Watanabe
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach out to this repeating world?
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの
Will these fleeting tears melt my black heart?
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these budding feelings resonate within my chest,
君の隣でずっと変わらず守るだろう
I will protect you forever by your side.
堕ちた希望を拾って 明日に繋いでゆけば
If I pick up the fallen hope and connect it to tomorrow,
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even the tangled, distorted wishes will unravel.
光をかざして 躊躇いを消した
I held up the light and banished my hesitation.
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you was the future,
泣いてる夜抱いたまま 嘆きを叫んで
holding the crying night and screaming my grief.
踏み出した足音 その向こう側へ そっと消してゆく
The footsteps I take, I'll gently erase them toward the other side.
確かな絆を強く握り進もう どこまでも
Let's move forward, gripping our certain bond tightly, wherever we go.
汚れきった奇跡を背に
With the dirtied miracle behind us.
作られた思い 触れれば何よりも
The fabricated feelings, if I touch them, they are more than anything...
温かくて現実が霞み始める
warm, and reality begins to haze.
震え出した世界に 問いかけ続けても
Even if I keep questioning this trembling world,
答えなんて出ないって もう君は知っていたの
you already knew that no answer would come.
泣いて滲んだ願いは 決して揺るがしはしなくて
The wishes blurred by tears will never be shaken,
ただそっと痛みを終りなく与える
only gently giving endless pain.
悲しみを知って 喜びを知った
Knowing sadness, knowing joy,
強さは君を 変えて立ち止まった時果て
strength changed you, and when you stood still, at the end of time,
全てを壊した 届くはずのない言葉を託して
everything was destroyed, entrusting words that should never reach.
見えた瞳は何を感じて遠ざける心 隠すように
What do those eyes feel, as if hiding a heart that pushes away?
今ここにいる意味 教えてくれたのなら
If you've taught me the meaning of being here now,
強く居られる 変わらずいつも
I can be strong, as always.
みんなー！今日は見に来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for coming to see me today!
oath sign
最後まで楽しんでいってねー！
Enjoy until the very end!
力をかざして
Holding up my power,
ためらいを消した
I've erased my hesitation.
あげたかったのは 未来で
What I wanted to give you was the future,
泣いてる夜 抱いたまま
while still embracing the nights of tears.
嘆きを叫んで
Shouting out my grief,
踏み出した足元
at my feet as I step forward,
遠くの理想が そっと 癒してゆく
a distant ideal gently heals me.
確かな絆を強く握り 誓おう
Let's swear, gripping our certain bond tightly.
どこまでも
No matter how far...
迷いなく 目を開いて
without any doubt, opening my eyes,
振り払って 手を伸ばそう
shaking it off, let's reach out our hands.
汚れきった 奇跡を 背に
With a stained miracle behind us.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 作詞・作曲 kemu
Haikei Doppelganger / Lyrics & Music: kemu
突如 鏡にボッシュート
Suddenly, I'm sucked into the mirror.
なんの冗談か目を擦ってみる
I rub my eyes, wondering if it's some joke.
影が脱ぎだして
My shadow starts to peel away,
どうせまた向こうは笑ってる
and the other side is surely laughing again.
もう一人自分がいたらって あなたは言いました
You said, "If only there were another me."
そんな真摯な願いが僕を呼んだのさ
That sincere wish is what called me here.
悔やんでがたとも 悲しきすべてのエージェント
Regret or not, oh, all you sorrowful agents.
片手間半端な覚悟 最低な意味不明な感情
A half-hearted resolve, the worst nonsensical emotions.
ねえこんなことに楽になる言葉があるんです
Hey, there's a word that makes all this easier.
123で代わってしまえば 僕は君のドッペル
Switch on 1, 2, 3 and I'll be your Doppelganger.
含み笑いで messiah you
With a smirk, I'm your messiah.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 君は君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who are you, who are you?
ああ混濁と交差して 僕は僕は誰？
Ah, crossing with confusion, who am I, who am I?
有無も言わせぬ 勧善懲悪は
An uncompromising poetic justice
居場所なんて残りはしない
leaves no place for anyone to stay.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 誰は誰は君？
Dear Doppelganger, who is who to you?
蝕まれちゃ存在に 世界が気付かない
The world doesn't notice a corroded existence.
嗚呼やまない ためもない
Ah, it doesn't stop, no hesitation.
奇跡の輪廻が 狂って 世界を埋め上げてるパッパッ
The cycle of miracles goes mad, filling up the world.
透明な顔が可笑しい 月曜日
A strange transparent face on a Monday.
ひとつふたつと崩れゆく つじつまが
One by one, the consistency crumbles away.
僕を疑いする
I start to doubt myself.
お前は一体誰だと
Asking, "Who the hell are you?"
ちょっと待って知らない 君の尻拭いなんて真っ平
Wait, I don't know you. I hate cleaning up your mess.
そうやって このまま 影は溶けゆく
And just like that, the shadow dissolves.
僕はなんなんだろう
What even am I?
ねえ どうか存在を返して
Hey, please, give me back my existence.
愛もサヨナラも ぐっちゃぐちゃで ゼンブここにあって
Love and goodbyes are all a mess, all here.
もうあなたはもうここにいないこと分かってるんでしょ
You already know you're not here anymore, right?
ねえ おわったの お前がいただけ
Hey, it's over. You were just there.
このまま前はなかった
There was no future from here.
含み笑いで messiah you
With a smirk, I'm your messiah.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 君は君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who are you, who are you?
ああ混濁と交差して 僕は僕は誰？
Ah, crossing with confusion, who am I, who am I?
嗚呼 独奏が震わせた
Ah, the solo performance made it tremble.
命の椅子は一つだけ
There's only one seat for life.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 誰は誰は君？
Dear Doppelganger, who is who to you?
零れ落ちた一粒を かき集める前に
Before gathering up a single fallen drop,
いたっていい 何でもいい
it's fine to exist, anything is fine.
器をください 狂った 世界が埋め上げてるパッパッ
Give me a vessel. The crazy world is filling up.
どうせ死ぬなら 誰にも知られないまま
If I'm to die anyway, I'd rather no one know.
夢に抱かれて 眠るように
Like falling asleep, embraced by a dream.
独りでいたいなら
If you want to be alone,
鏡の中の 偽物として
as a fake inside the mirror,
僕のほうがちゃんと 君を演じてやるから
I'll play the part of you much better,
君の続きの誰か ちゃんと救わなくちゃ
so I must save whoever follows you.
僕はわかっているんだろう 何をすればいいかさ
I suppose I know what I should do.
どうか誰か僕に奇跡をくれよ
Please, someone, give me a miracle.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 君は君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who are you, who are you?
ああ混濁と交差して 僕は僕は誰？
Ah, crossing with confusion, who am I, who am I?
もう止まらない 戻れない
I can't stop anymore, can't go back.
どうもこんにちは 君の
Well, hello there. I'm yours...
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 誰は誰は僕？
Dear Doppelganger, who is who to me?
蝕まれちゃ存在に 世界が気付かない
The world doesn't notice a corroded existence.
どうだい？ 奇跡の人形が
How is it? The miracle doll...
狂った世界を褒め上げるザ
...praises the crazy world.
うまくやれよランバッパ
Do it well, rambappa.
「どうも、ボク君の分身です」
"Hello, I am your alter ego."
みんなー！ 盛り上がってこー！
Everyone! Let's get excited!
考え抜く このままいつまで 隠しておけるかな
Pondering, how long can I keep it hidden like this?
帰りたくなった時 サヨナラは言えるかな
When I want to go home, will I be able to say goodbye?
見落とした あの日のサインが 少しずつ溶けても
Even if the sign of that day I overlooked melts away little by little,
きっと大丈夫だよ こうやって僕らは歌えるから
I'm sure it'll be okay, because we can sing like this.
目を閉じる 小さな祈りに まだ残せるかな
Closing my eyes, can I still leave something in a small prayer?
光が戻った時 ただいまは言えるから
When the light returns, I'll be able to say "I'm home."
行かなくちゃ 世界で一番 綺麗なものなら
I must go, if it's the most beautiful thing in the world.
今まで奪われてた分は 取り戻すまでさ
Until I take back what was stolen until now.
もっとクラクラクラクラさせてよ
Make me feel more and more dizzy,
ユラユラユラユラをみててよ
look at the swaying, swaying, swaying,
キラキラキラキラめいていてよ
keep sparkling, sparkling, sparkling.
そっと傷ついた夜を呼び出してみる 鮮やかな魔法をひとつかける
Gently calling out the night that was hurt, I'll cast a vivid spell.
それだけで僕らは飛べるのさ
Just with that, we can fly.
離さないでよ 眼差しを 僕たちはもう止まらないよ
Don't let go of your gaze, we won't stop anymore.
魔法が解ける それまで 繋いでいてよ 手を 手を
Until the spell is broken, keep holding on, our hands, our hands.
ひとつだって残さない すべてを取り戻すだけさ
I won't leave even one behind, I'll just take everything back.
魔法が解ける それまで 繋いでいてよ 手を 手を テオ
Until the spell is broken, keep holding on, our hands, our hands, Teo.
みんな！ もっと盛り上がってー！
Everyone! Get more excited!
今まで奪われてた分は 取り戻すまでさ
Until I take back what was stolen until now.
そっと傷ついた夜を呼び出してみる 鮮やかな魔法をひとつかける
Gently calling out the night that was hurt, I'll cast a vivid spell.
それだけで僕らは飛べるのさ
Just with that, we can fly.
もっとクラクラクラクラさせてよ
Make me feel more and more dizzy,
ユラユラユラユラをみててよ
look at the swaying, swaying, swaying,
キラキラキラキラめいていてよ
keep sparkling, sparkling, sparkling.
離さないでよ 眼差しを 僕たちはもう止まらないよ
Don't let go of your gaze, we won't stop anymore.
魔法が解ける それまで 繋いでいてよ 手を 手を
Until the spell is broken, keep holding on, our hands, our hands.
ひとつだって残さない すべてを取り戻すだけさ
I won't leave even one behind, I'll just take everything back.
魔法が解ける それまで 繋いでいてよ 手を 手を テオ
Until the spell is broken, keep holding on, our hands, our hands, Teo.
みなさん！ こんにちはー！ ときのそらでーす！
Everyone! Hello! I'm Tokino Sora!
開幕から3曲歌わせていただきましたー！
I sang three songs right from the opening!
みんな見えてる？ 聞こえてる？
Can everyone see? Can everyone hear?
コメントたくさんありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for all the comments!
Hello everyone!
今日見に来てくれて、とっても嬉しいです！
I'm so happy you came to see me today!
今の『テオ』、画面の映像どうでしたか？
How was the visual on the screen for 'Teo' just now?
すごい綺麗な演出もあったんですけど、見てくれたかなみんな？
There was a really beautiful production, did everyone see it?
あとは、ステージも見て！
Also, look at the stage!
すごい！ めちゃくちゃ豪華！
Amazing! It's so luxurious!
こんな素敵なステージを作ってくださって、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for making such a wonderful stage!
そしてみんながね、こうやってコメントしてくれてるの、とっても嬉しいよ！ ありがとう、ありがとう！
And everyone, I'm so happy you're commenting like this! Thank you, thank you!
さあ、そんな今日なんですが、是非是非...
So, about today, please, please...
こちらときのそら生誕祭ライブで...
during this Tokino Sora Birthday Live...
呟いてもらえたらとっても嬉しいなって思います！
I'd be so happy if you could tweet about it!
お誕生日おめでとうありがとうございます！
Thank you for all the birthday wishes!
ハロー、ハロー！
Hello, hello!
にゃあ、なんかすごい最初からね...
Meow, it's like, from the very beginning...
3曲全力疾走みたいな感じで歌わせていただきましたが...
I've been singing three songs at full speed...
今日はですね、いっぱい曲を歌って...
but today, I'm going to sing a lot of songs...
私のワンマンライブみたいなイメージで
like a solo live concert,
ちょっとね、色々歌っていこうかなと思っています。
I'm thinking of singing all sorts of things.
たくさんの歌を歌っていくので...
I'll be singing many songs...
是非是非最後まで楽しんでもらえると嬉しいなと思いますし...
so I hope you enjoy it until the very end...
まあね、この後には、最後の方にはちょっと...
And, well, towards the end of this...
ちょっと何か見せたいものもあったりするからね、見ててくださいね！
there's something I want to show you, so please keep watching!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
今日初めて私を知ったっていう人も、是非是非見てもらえると嬉しいよー！
Even if this is the first time you've seen me today, I'd be so happy if you watched!
さ、次の曲はね、みんなにまったりと聞いてもらいたいなと思ってるので...
Now, for the next song, I'd like everyone to listen to it in a relaxed way...
ちょっと衣装も変えちゃおっかなー、なんて思ってます。
so I'm thinking of changing my costume as well.
とりあえず真ん中に移動しようかなー！
For now, I'll move to the center!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
見えてるよ！
I can see you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんな見て！
Everyone, look!
見えてる？見えてる？見えてる？
Can you see? Can you see? Can you see?
見えてる？ありがとう！
Can you see? Thank you!
大好きだよ！コメントもありがとう！
I love you! Thank you for the comments too!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
大好きだよ！
I love you!
これからしっとりした歌を歌うから、いっぱい聞いてもらえると嬉しいです。
I'll be singing some mellow songs now, so I'd be happy if you listened to them a lot.
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
それでは聴いてください。
Now, please listen.
「プロローグ」。
"Prologue."
プロローグ / 作詞・作曲 Uru
Prologue / Lyrics & Composition: Uru
目に掛かる髪の毛と　掻き分けた指
Hair falling over eyes, and fingers that brushed it aside
壊れそうでどこか寂しげな背中
A back that looked fragile and somehow lonely
頼りない太陽を　滲ませながら
While the unreliable sun was blurred
微笑んだその横顔を見つめていた
I was staring at that profile as it smiled
いつの間にかその全て
Before I knew it,
視界に入ってくるの
all of it came into my view
心が波打つ痛みに　どうして気付いてしまったの
Why did I notice the pain of my heart rippling?
あなたを探してる　隠した瞳の奥で
I'm searching for you, deep within my hidden eyes
誰にも見えぬように　行き場もなくて
So that no one can see, with nowhere to go
彷徨いながら　あなたを見る世界は
While wandering, the world where I see you
いつでも綺麗だった
Was always beautiful
空には一つだけ
In the sky, just one
淡く光る小さな星が残ってる
A small star faintly glowing remains
...放なす 夢見ない心
...lets go, a heart that doesn't dream
見つめられるほどに 嘘がつけない
The more you look at me, the more I cannot lie
力なく点滅する あの街灯を
That streetlight flickering powerlessly
見上げてたその横顔は 優しかった
The profile of you looking up was kind
破れそうに膨らんで
Swollen to bursting
真っ赤に熟れた果実は
and ripened deep red, the fruit
誰かの摘む手を待っている
Is waiting for someone's hand to pick it
ねぇ それは私だった
Hey, that was me
あなたが溢れていく
You overflow,
抑えた胸の数だけ
by the amount of suppressed feelings in my chest
隠せない始まりを
Conveying the unhideable beginning
過ぎた月へ
to the moon that has passed
手のひらに伝えてゆくよ
Into the palm of my hand
風は冷たいのに そんな心は赤いままに
Though the wind is cold, such a heart remains red
あなたに触れたいと思ってしまった どうして
I ended up wanting to touch you, why?
二人でいたの
Were we together?
痛くて 苦しくて それなら
It hurts, it's painful, if so
見えないようにどこかへ 飛んでゆけ
Fly away somewhere so I can't see you
そう思うのに
Though I think that
あなたを探してる 何度も
I'm searching for you, many times
名前を呼んで
Calling your name
空には一つだけ
In the sky, only one
淡く光る小さな星を浮かべて
Small star floating, shining faintly
Beyond
作詞・作曲：星野寿菜子
Lyrics & Music: Sunako Hoshino
夕映えに揺らゆたう
Swaying in the sunset glow,
少し伸びた前髪と影法師
slightly grown bangs and a silhouette
巡る日々 楽しかった分だけ
The revolving days, as much as they were enjoyable
今日が終わってしまうことがどうしても
That today is ending, no matter what
寂しくなるけど
It makes me lonely, but...
忘れないで 同じ空を
Don't forget that the same sky
見上げていること
We are looking up at
どんな君だって 愛しく思うから
Because I love you, whoever you are
大丈夫 大丈夫だって歌うから
I'll sing that it's okay, that it's okay
変わりゆく中で 変わらない気持ちで
Amidst the changing, with unchanging feelings
ずっと 大丈夫だって歌うから
I'll always sing that it's okay
時間も距離も超えて心は
Crossing time and distance, my heart
そばにあるから
Will be by your side
五月雨に濡れて
Wet by the early summer rain,
凍えた爪先じゃ歩けずに
unable to walk with frozen toes
惑う日々 悲しかった分だけ
Wandering days, as much as they were sad
明日が少しでも輝くように
So that tomorrow shines, even just a little
...輝くように
...to shine bright.
いつでも
Always,
願っているから
because I'm wishing for it.
一緒に かけがえのない時間を
Let's spend these irreplaceable moments together,
重ねていこうよ
and build them up.
どこまでも
No matter how far,
頑張れない日も
even on days when you can't try your best,
涙が出ない夜も
or on nights when tears won't come,
大丈夫 大丈夫だって
it's okay, I'll say "it's okay,"
歌うから
as I sing.
新しい一歩
When you take a new step,
君が踏み出すときも
when you're about to move forward,
ちゃんと大丈夫だって
I'll properly say "it's okay,"
歌うから
as I sing.
そう ちっぽけな僕ら
That's right, small as we are,
こころ
our hearts...
揺れながらも
...might waver, but...
大切を重ねて
...let's gather what's important,
未来を
and the future...
描こう
...let's paint it.
どんな僕だって
No matter what kind of person I am,
愛してくれたこと
you loved me.
いつだって いつだって
Always, always,
忘れないから
I'll never forget it.
変わりゆく中で
In this changing world,
変わらない気持ちで
with unchanging feelings,
僕の精一杯で
with all my might,
返すから
I'll give back to you.
どんな君だって
No matter what kind of person you are,
愛おしく思うから
I'll hold you dear.
大丈夫 大丈夫だって
So it's okay, I'll say "it's okay,"
歌うから
as I sing.
たどり着いた今日に
In this "today" we've reached,
君という光に会えた
I met the light that is you.
だから
That's why...
大丈夫だって歌うから
...I'll sing that it's okay.
時間も
Time,
距離も
distance...
越えて心は
...transcending them, my heart...
そばに
...is by your side,
あるから
always.
はい！ありがとうございました！
Yes! Thank you very much!
ここでは、「ポラリス」「Beyond」と、2曲続けて歌わせていただきました。
I just sang "Polaris" and "Beyond" in a row.
いやあ、バラードをね、挑戦したいなと思って。
Man, I really wanted to try singing ballads.
今回はね、いろんな挑戦を、色々やっていこうというわけで。
For this event, I decided to take on various challenges.
最初の3曲は... おっとっと、ああ、大丈夫だ。
The first three songs were... Whoops! Oh, it's okay.
最初の3曲は、なんていうんだろうな。
The first three songs were, how should I put it...
自分の中で難しいと思っていた、早くて高くて、みたいな。
Songs I found difficult, with fast tempos and high notes.
でもかっこよくて、みたいな。そういう曲。あ、パチパチ皆さんありがとうございます！
But they were cool too. Oh, thank you for the applause!
を、選んでみまして。
Those were the ones I chose.
次のゾーンは、えー、もう...なんて言うんでしょうね。
The next section was, well, how should I say...
バラード。普段あんまり挑戦することのない、バラードを歌ってみました。
Ballads. I tried songs I don't usually sing often.
皆盛り上がって... 「盛り上がってる」っていう曲じゃないけど、盛り上がってるー？
Is everyone hyped? They aren't hype songs, but are you?
そして、なんと！初めて、この真ん中のステージを使いました！
And I used this center stage for the first time!
皆、こっちのステージも見てよー！
Everyone, check out this stage too!
かわいい！
It's so cute!
あ、なんか上にも、もうなんかありますね。
Oh, look, there's something up there too.
これは、これじゃ何だろうね？ということで。
I wonder what this is? Anyway...
あ、ありがとうございます。感動ありがとう。いや、こちらこそありがとうございます！
Oh, thank you. No, thank *you* guys!
いや、みんなたくさんコメントして、たくさん呟いてってねー！
Please keep commenting and tweeting a lot!
いっぱい呟いてくれると、いっぱいチャットしてくれると、私とっても嬉しい！
It makes me so happy when you tweet and chat!
そして、ぜ、こんな豪華になったステージなんですが、
And, although the stage has become so grand...
よく見るといろんなところにね、工夫がありまして。
if you look closely, there are many little details.
例えばね、こっちかな？
For example, over here maybe?
ここの... あ、そうそうこれ！カメラマンさんありがとうございます！
This part... Ah, yes, this! Thank you, cameraman!
こちら、あん肝と星街が、いるところとかね。そう。
Like this spot with Ankimo and Hoshigane. Yeah.
なんか、あん肝はね、どこでも見守ってくれているみたいな感じなんですよね。
It's like Ankimo is watching over me from everywhere.
後ろの方もとっても可愛いですね。
The back area is very cute too.
お水飲みました。
I took a water break.
そして、そして、
And then, and then...
この全体を見ると、ここにね、
if you look at the whole thing, right here...
こういうのがあったりとか。
there are things like this.
水色とピンクで、もうね、全体的にピンクと水色を、
With light blue and pink... I made the stage use
すごいメインに使ったステージに。
pink and light blue as the main colors.
...なっています。
...it has become.
やあ、こんな素敵なステージでね
Yeah, on such a wonderful stage
歌えるなんて本当に幸せですし
I'm really happy to be able to sing,
こんなにたくさんのコメントでみんなと一緒に盛り上がっていけるのも楽しいです。
and it's also fun to be able to get excited with everyone through so many comments.
本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
さあ、次はどんな...
Now, what kind of...
...姿になっているのかな？
...appearance will I have next?
衣装チェンジ、しちゃおうかな？
Shall I do a costume change?
ありがとう！見えてるー！
Thank you! I can see you!
二階のみんなー！
Everyone on the second floor!
奥のみんなー！
Everyone in the back!
そして、コメントもー！
And the comments too!
みんなー！
Everyone!
こんな素敵なステージでみんなとお誕生日配信ができて
To be able to do this birthday stream with everyone on such a wonderful stage
幸せだー！ありがとうー！
I'm so happy! Thank you!
いつも見てくれてありがとうね。
Thank you for always watching.
みんなが曲とかフリ覚えて、こうやって見に来てくれてるの
Everyone remembering the songs and moves and coming to see me like this
本当に嬉しいよ！
It makes me really happy!
ありがとう！嬉しい嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy, so happy!
あん肝ー！
Ankimo!
あん肝ー！あん肝ー！あん肝ー！
Ankimo! Ankimo! Ankimo!
ぺっぺっぺっ
Pe pe pe
何で？えっえっえっ
Why? Eh? Eh? Eh?
というわけで
So,
なんと、ここからはあん肝と一緒にステージをやりたいなと思ってて
well, from here on, I'd like to do the stage together with Ankimo.
踊れる？あん肝。練習してきた？
Can you dance, Ankimo? Did you practice?
本当？本当？
Really? Really?
というわけで、ここからはあん肝と一緒に...
So, from here on, with Ankimo...
いじめてないよ！これは私の愛情表現。あん肝、私の愛情表現だから。
I'm not bullying him! This is my expression of love. Ankimo, it's my expression of love.
ね、ね。
Right? Right?
ちょっと飲み物持ってくるね。
I'm going to go grab a drink.
じゃあ、ここからは一緒に踊っていこうか！
Then, let's dance together from here on!
それじゃあ, いくよ！
Alright, here we go!
それでは聴いてください、ユメゾラ☆ファンファーレ！
Now please listen to: Yumezora Fanfare!
約束した今日の日を
This day we promised,
一生忘れない そんな気がした
I felt I'd never forget it for the rest of my life
ユメゾラの真下で
Right under the dream sky
ユメゾラ☆ファンファーレ
作詞:まつもとななみ 作曲・編曲:藤原彩豊
Yumezora Fanfare
Lyrics: Nanami Matsumoto Composition/Arrangement: Ayato Fujiwara
あの空の向こうまで行ってみたいなって
I want to go beyond that sky
覗き込んだ望遠鏡 宝探しみたいだ
Peering through the telescope is like a treasure hunt
「好き」が夢を叶えるって誰かが言ってた
Someone said that "liking" something makes dreams come true
思い切り泣いたり笑ったり
Crying and laughing as hard as I can
全力前進でしょう
Full speed ahead, right?
あぁ夜明けが星座を追い越した時
Ah, when the dawn overtook the constellations
流れる星が光った
A shooting star shone
一つだけ願うのなら 夢が叶う瞬間
If I could make just one wish, at the moment a dream comes true
そばにいてくれますか？
Will you be by my side?
見に行こう ハッピーエンドのファンファーレ
Let's go see the fanfare of the happy ending
キラキラの未来へ
To a sparkling future
星に負けない光と 昂る希望響かせ
With a light that rivals the stars, let rising hope resound
涙と涙が重なって 空が明けるように
As tears and tears overlap, just like the dawn breaking in the sky
夢と夢がギュッと重なる瞬間を
The moment when dreams and dreams overlap tightly
奇跡と呼ぶんだ
Is what we call a miracle
Hey! ありがとう!
Hey! Thank you!
はい! はい!
Hey! Hey!
着地点は いつだって
The place I land is always
君のその笑顔
that smile of yours.
遠回りしたけど出会えたんだ
I took a long way around, but I finally met you.
一緒 一緒でしょ
We're together, we're together, right?
きらめく希望のメロディー描いて
Drawing a melody of sparkling hope,
夢に会いに行こう
let's go to meet our dreams.
無数の星屑の中
Among countless stardust,
見つけてくれてありがとう
thank you for finding me.
大切なキミへいつの日でも
To you, my precious one, no matter the day,
一番に届けよう
I'll deliver this to you first.
見てて 私 ここで歌い続けること
Watch me, I will keep singing here,
約束するから
I promise you that.
みんな!
Everyone!
約束通り、また歌ったよ!
Just as I promised, I sang again!
ありがとう!
Thank you!
キミの声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear your voice
近くで
from close by.
道を照らす月のように
Like the moon illuminating the path,
(ずっと ずっと ずっと)
(Forever, and ever, and ever)
ハッピーエンドのファンファーレ
The fanfare of a happy ending,
一緒に叶えよう
let's fulfill it together.
見たことのない世界へ
To a world never seen before,
ステップ踏んで飛び出そう
let's step out and fly away.
笑顔と笑顔が重なって
When smiles overlap with smiles,
虹が架かるように
like a rainbow appearing.
夢と夢がギュッと重なる瞬間を
The moment dreams overlap tightly,
奇跡と呼ぶんだ
we call it a miracle.
行こうよ ユメゾラの向こうへ
Let's go, beyond the dream sky.
さあ!
Now!
こちらもホスフェスで歌った曲です!
This is another song I sang at HosuFes!
愛言葉IV!
Ai Kotoba IV!
みんなも盛り上がっていってね!
Everyone, get excited with me!
贈呈なんてしてなかった現状
The current state where I hadn't given anything,
君もそう思った？
did you think so too?
最高で止まらないように更新したい
I want to keep updating so it doesn't stop at the best,
叶えたい夢まであとどれくらい
How much longer until the dream I want to fulfill,
誰も行ったことがない場所へ
to a place where no one has ever been?
辿り着くまでは僕ら止まれない
Until we reach it, we cannot stop.
多分しつこいけどどうかよろしくね
I'm probably persistent, but please bear with me.
ねえねえ たまに めーめー
Hey hey, sometimes 'meeh meeh',
僕だけじゃ作れないもの
something I can't create by myself.
僕とか君とか私とか恋とか愛とかまとめて全部
Me, you, I, love, affection, everything all together,
君がどこかに行っちゃうとかありえないよ
it's impossible that you would go somewhere else.
君がくれた音に弾けた火花
The sparks that burst from the sound you gave me,
「はじめまして」からずっと恋しちゃってるんだよ
I've been in love with you ever since our first meeting.
君のいない未来考えられないよ
I can't imagine a future without you.
これから先もふたりがいいな
I want the two of us to be together from now on too.
一途になるほど冷えたくもなったよ
The more earnest I became, the more I wanted to cool down,
散々な僕のこと呼んでくれてありがとう
thank you for calling out to someone as terrible as me.
君のいない未来考えられないよ
I can't imagine a future without you.
これから先もふたりで
From now on, the two of us,
それがいいじゃん
that would be nice, wouldn't it?
もっと膨らんでくストーリー
The story keeps expanding more and more,
感傷やけに凹んじゃって
feeling sentimental and unusually depressed.
大丈夫求めすぎは野暮
It's okay, asking for too much is unrefined,
終わんない愛の連綿どーでしょ
how about a continuous love that never ends?
ねえねえ おいで めーめー
Hey hey, come here, 'meeh meeh',
僕が君にできること
what I can do for you,
まだまだまだあるけど
there's still much more,
驚かせたいからないしょなんだ
but it's a secret because I want to surprise you.
君の愛がいつも勝っちゃうこと
That your love always wins,
許さないよ
I won't allow that.
せーの！
One, two!
君以外はやだ
I don't want anyone but you
わわわわ
Wa wa wa wa
ただ変わらないトキメキを
Just an unchanging excitement
絶好調しちゃうのはバカ
Feeling on top of the world is silly
君がくれた音に弾けた光に
In the sound you gave me, in the light that popped
はじめましてからずっと恋しちゃってるんだよ
I've been in love with you ever since our first 'Nice to meet you'
君のいない未来考えられないよ
I can't imagine a future without you
これから先も二人でいいじゃん
It's fine if it's just the two of us from now on, right?
意地になるほど逃げたくもなったよ
I wanted to run away so much it made me stubborn
散々な僕のこと呼んでくれてありがとう
Thank you for calling out to me when I was a mess
君のいない未来考えられないよ
I can't imagine a future without you
これから先も二人でそれがいいじゃん
It's better if it's just the two of us from now on
愛と言葉で遊ぼうよ
Let's play with love and words
ドキドキしたいじゃん
I want to feel my heart pound
誰だってあーだーこーだー言って
Everyone says this and that
甘酸っぱくなっちゃった
And it turned bittersweet
実らないキスは離れない
The unfulfilled kiss won't leave me
僕ら曖昧よ
We're ambiguous
言い澱んじゃっていいよ
It's okay to hesitate
不意にだって恋のせいじゃん
Even if it's sudden, it's because of love, right?
なんだってだって君が
No matter what, it's because you
輝けるように
Are able to shine
はい！というわけで、「夢空ファンファーレ」と「愛言葉IV」でしたー！
Alright! That was 'Yumezora Fanfare' and 'Akotoba IV'!
イエーイ！
Yay!
4thフェスで歌ったね。この「Bright」衣装で。
I sang those at 4th fes. In this 'Bright' costume.
やあ、どうでしたか？
Well, how was it?
いや、ここでは4thフェスの再現がしたいなと思って、ちょっとね、歌いました。
I wanted to recreate 4th fes here, so I sang them for a bit.
4thフェス、みんな、思い出したかな？
Did everyone remember 4th fes?
イエーイ！
Yay!
そして、あん肝！ありがとう！
And Ankimo! Thank you!
あん肝も一生懸命踊ってくれました。イエーイ！
Ankimo also danced his best. Yay!
拍手拍手、ありがとうございます。
Clap, clap, thank you very much.
やっぱね、この「Bright」衣装で、やっぱ4thフェスの曲がどうしても歌いたかったっていう気持ちがありまして。
I really had the feeling that I definitely wanted to sing 4th fes songs in this 'Bright' costume.
それで、ここに入れました。
So, I included them here.
はあ…息が…息が切れちゃう。あん肝待って。
Haa... I'm... I'm out of breath. Ankimo, wait.
ただいま。
I'm back.
なんか…なんか…なんかアピールしてた？
Was... was he... was he appealing for something?
アピールしてた？私の誕生日なんだけど。
Was he? It's my birthday, though.
アピールしてた？「あん肝の誕生日だぞ」と思ってた？
Was he? Were you thinking 'It's Ankimo's birthday'?
そんなことない？
No?
そして、この後なんですが…
And, after this...
さらに実はサプライズが…
Actually, there's a further surprise...
あー！ない！って言ったらどうなると思う、みんな。
Ah! What would you do if I said there wasn't one?
びっくりするかな？あはは。
Would you be surprised? Ahaha.
あります！
There is one!
えーね、昨日もね、あの予想配信とかもしたんですけど、
Well, yesterday I did a prediction stream too,
サムネのこのロゴにもちょっとね、ヒントがあるということでね、
And there's a bit of a hint in this logo on the thumbnail too,
みんな、どんなのが来るかなー？っていうのを楽しみに待っててね。
Everyone, please look forward to what's coming next.
ガクガクじゃないよ、みんな。
It's not 'Gaku gaku', everyone.
それでは、次の曲、何だと思いますかー？
Now then, what do you think the next song is?
何かなー？何かなー？
What could it be? What could it be?
みんなわかるかなー？
Does everyone know?
逆にびっくりだよね。逆にびっくりだよね。
It's surprising, isn't it? Surprising in a different way.
じゃあ次の曲はアップテンポな曲にしておこうかな！
Well, I think I'll make the next song an up-tempo one!
一緒に盛り上がっていこうー！
Let's get hyped together!
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
Hey DJ, かませ yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ, let it rip yeah yeah yeah
気分上々の針を落とせ
Drop the needle on that high-spirited feeling
音鳴らせ パーティーナイト
Let the music play, party night
No more cry cry cry
みんなで踊れ
Everybody dance
Hip-hop, pop
駆け抜けろミラクルナンバー
Run through that miracle number
イエーイ！あん肝ラップ、よろしく！
Yay! Ankimo, take the rap!
Yo, この時代に分かち合うミュージック
Yo, music we share in this era
踊り明かしたくて回す地球儀
I want to dance all night and spin the globe.
Good Luck 不安定生活 それだからバランス重視
Good luck with an unstable life, that's why I focus on balance.
良い事ばかりじゃないから 頑張れる
It's because it's not all good things that I can do my best.
最悪な日に効く 再起動のボタンクリック
Click the restart button that works on the worst days.
DJ かけて今すぐ MIX
DJ, play it, MIX it right now.
洒落てるビートに乗って 感じる形揺らそうよ
Ride the stylish beat, let's shake the way we feel.
Hey DJ カマセ Yeah Yeah Yeah 気分上々↑↑の
Hey DJ, let's go! Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! My mood is soaring high!
針落とせ Party Night 止まらない
Drop the needle, Party Night, it won't stop.
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly みんなで踊れ
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly, everyone dance!
Hip Hop Pop かけてよ ミラーボール・ナンバー
Play Hip Hop Pop, that Mirror Ball Number.
新衣装ー！Hey!
New outfit! Hey!
青・白！Hey!
Blue and white! Hey!
青・白！
Blue and white!
Hip Hop Pop はずむは 鼓動の果て
Hip Hop Pop, bouncing to the end of the heartbeat.
十字路で 今を楽しみたいね
At the crossroads, I want to enjoy the moment.
リズム探して 良いポイント それぞれの色重ね合わそ
Looking for the rhythm, the good point, let's layer our respective colors.
君と手と手重ねて 苦しむ筈の果て
With your hand in mine, at the end where we were supposed to suffer,
十字路で 今を楽しみたいね
At the crossroads, I want to enjoy the moment.
Let's Party はじけるわ
Let's Party, it's popping!
洒落てるフローに乗って 頭の中揺さぶる
Ride the stylish flow, shaking inside your head.
Hey DJ 洒落て Yeah Yeah Yeah 気分上々↑↑の
Hey DJ, stylish, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! My mood is soaring high!
波に乗って 弾け飛べ Party Night
Ride the wave, pop off, Party Night!
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly みんなで踊れ
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly, everyone dance!
Hip Hop Pop 朝まで ミラーボール・ナンバー
Play Hip Hop Pop, until morning, Mirror Ball Number.
ミラーボール スモークの匂い
Mirror ball, the smell of smoke,
溶けるようなハーモニー
like a melting harmony.
身にまとって 踊り明かす がむしゃらなままで
Wrap it around yourself and dance all night, staying reckless.
Hey DJ カマセ Yeah Yeah Yeah 気分上々↑↑の
Hey DJ, let's go! Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! My mood is soaring high!
針落とせ Party Night 止まらない
Drop the needle, Party Night, it won't stop.
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly みんなで踊れ
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly, everyone dance!
Hip Hop Pop かけてよ ミラーボール・ナンバー
Play Hip Hop Pop, that Mirror Ball Number.
Hey DJ 洒落て Yeah Yeah Yeah 気分上々↑↑の
Hey DJ, stylish, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! My mood is soaring high!
波に乗って 弾け飛べ Party Night
Ride the wave, pop off, Party Night!
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly みんなで踊れ
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly, everyone dance!
朝まで ミラーボール・ナンバー
Until morning, Mirror Ball Number.
Hey DJ カマセ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Hey DJ, let's go! Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly
カマセ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's go! Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly
カマセ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's go! Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly
カマセ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Let's go! Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!
Roll-ly, Roll-ly, Roll-ly
Hey DJ カマセ Yeah Yeah Yeah
Hey DJ, let's go! Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!
はい！ということで、気分上々でした！
Yes! And that was 'Kibun Joujou'!
そして、新衣装だ！やったよー、あんきも。新衣装が来た！
And it's a new outfit! We did it, Ankimo. A new outfit has arrived!
やったー！
Yay!
というわけで、はい。あのね、昨日の配信でも...
So, yes. You know, in yesterday's stream too...
えー、いろいろと予想があって、すごい似てる人が多くてびっくりしちゃいましたね。
um, there were various predictions, and I was surprised by how many people guessed correctly.
やっぱこういう衣装がみんな良かったのかなっていう感じで。
I guess everyone liked this kind of outfit.
はい、早速ね、ちょっとずつ見せていこうかなって思います。
Yes, I'd like to show it to you bit by bit right away.
まず下側ですね。見て、ブーツ。
First, the bottom half. Look, the boots.
ブーツ、ブーツに私のモチーフの星が入ってます。
The boots, there are stars, my motif, on the boots.
そしてね、レースですね。
And then, the lace.
こちら、レースの靴下。
Here, lace socks.
めっちゃ可愛い、ありがとう！
They're so cute, thank you!
そして、ちょっとね、足がいっぱい見えんの恥ずかしいんですけど、
And, it's a bit embarrassing to show so much of my legs, but,
からの、こちら、パンツスタイル。
following that, here's the pants style.
からの、ほら！ロゴのね、この色っていうのが、あちこちに使われております。
And, look! This color from the logo is used here and there.
ね？
Right?
そして、実はこの胸元のパーカーなんですけど、
And, actually, about this hoodie around the chest area,
胸元のところには、えー、あんきもとぬんぬんのなんか何これ？
on the chest part, um, there's Ankimo and Nun-Nun's... what is this?
お団子みたいにあって、で、ぬんぬんって書いてあります。
They're like dumplings, and it says 'Nun-Nun'.
からの、ネックレスとチョーカーをつけました。
Also, I put on a necklace and a choker.
ぬふっ。
Hehe.
そして、上は帽子ですね。
And, on top is a hat.
こっち、こっちか。
This side, this way.
星が入っていて、ね。ここにアンキモとヌンヌンがいます。
Stars are on it, see. And here are Ankimo and Nun-nun.
そして、後ろですね。後ろのシルエットこんな感じです。全体で見るとこんな感じですね。
And then, the back. The back silhouette looks like this. When you look at the whole thing, it's like this.
で、ちょっと横から見るとわかるかな。ここ、フードをつけてるんですけど、あ、フードの形これなんだろうね。
And, maybe you can tell if you look from the side. I'm wearing a hoodie here, but oh, what's this shape of the hood?
なんだろうね、これは、ね、アンキモ、ね。
I wonder what it is. This is, right, Ankimo?
で、このフードがどんな感じになっているかは明日の振り返り配信でお披露目したいと思っているので、
And as for how this hood looks, I'm planning to reveal it during tomorrow's recap stream,
ぜひぜひ明日も見に来てくれると嬉しいです。よろしくね。
so I'd be very happy if you could come and watch tomorrow too. Please join me!
そうそう、アンキ...あれ？あれ？アンキモ...どっちのアンキモとさっき歌ったんだっけ？わかんない。増えた。
That's right, Anki... Huh? Oh? Ankimo... which Ankimo did I sing with just now? I don't know. They've increased.
アンキモも増えましたね。
The Ankimo have increased too.
そしてね、見てください、ステージも見てくださいよ。ちょっとね、変わったの気づきますか？
And also, please look, look at the stage as well. Did you notice a little change?
アンキモたちがね、DJキュッキュッキュッキュッキュッキュッてやって、ヌンヌンがね、ちょっと
The Ankimo are doing some DJing, "kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu-kyu", and Nun-nun is...
ヘッドホンつけたりとかしておりますね。ヌンヌンも盛り上がっておるよ。
wearing headphones and stuff. Nun-nun is also getting hyped!
ということで、ここからはちょっと盛り上がる曲を歌っていきたいなと思っています。
So, from here on, I'd like to sing some songs that will get everyone hyped.
次の曲いってみよう！
Let's go to the next song!
だんだんなあ ほどがよくない
It's gradually getting... not so good.
大問題ね だってばよくなくない？
It's a big problem, right? Because it's not good, is it?
もっとが聴きたい
I want to hear more.
最高更新中
Setting a new personal best.
サラマンダー 作詞・作曲：DECO*27
Salamander - Lyrics/Composition: DECO*27
サラマンダー
Salamander
いっぱい欲しい 癖になるなんてずるいじゃない ねえ
I want it all. It's not fair that it's so addictive, you know?
知ってたんなら 先に伝いといてほしいかな ねえ
If you knew, I wish you had told me sooner, you know?
もう降参です ハマっちゃって 君なしじゃダメダメになっちゃって
I give up now. I'm hooked, I can't do anything without you.
リピっちゃいたい ピリっちゃいたい おかわりできるから もう一回
I want to repeat it. I want that tingle. Since I can have a second helping, one more time!
サラマンダー ほどがよくない
Salamander. It's not so good.
大問題ね だってばよくなくない？
It's a big problem, right? Because it's not good, is it?
もっとが聴きたい
I want to hear more.
最高更新中
Setting a new personal best.
やめられないのよ
I can't stop.
やめたくないのよ
I don't want to stop.
ちゃんとフゥして 火傷したくないなら
Blow on it properly if you don't want to get burned.
サラマンダー
Salamander
何回でも メラメラになって仕上がりたい ねえ
As many times as it takes, I want to flare up and be done, you know?
行き過ぎちゃって アチチチ ちょい猫舌ならご面倒くさい
Going too far, it's hot-hot-hot. If you're a bit sensitive to heat, it's a hassle.
リピっちゃいたい ピリっちゃいたい おかわりできるから もう一回
I want to repeat it. I want that tingle. Since I can have a second helping, one more time!
サラマンダー ほどがよくない
Salamander. It's not so good.
大問題ね だってばよくなくない？
It's a big problem, right? Because it's not good, is it?
もっとが聴きたい
I want to hear more.
ちょうだい
Give it to me.
サラマンダー ほとにダメじゃん
Salamander. It's really no good, is it?
絶好調ね 正直だせなくない？
In top form, right? To be honest, isn't it hard to hide it?
本音が聴きたい
I want to hear your true feelings.
最高更新中
Setting a new personal best.
やめられないのよ
I can't stop.
やめたくないのよ
I don't want to stop.
ちゃんとフゥして 火傷したくないなら
Blow on it properly if you don't want to get burned.
抜け出したいけど
I want to get out, but...
抜け出せないのよ
I can't get out.
ちゃんとフゥして 火傷したくないなら
Blow on it properly if you don't want to get burned.
サラマンダー
Salamander
ちゃんとフゥして 火傷したくないなら
Blow on it properly if you don't want to get burned.
みんな盛り上がって！ハイ！
Everyone, get hyped! High!
エレクトリカル・サーフィン 作詞・作曲：美波嶺
Electrical Surfing - Lyrics/Composition: Minamine
サーフィン！サーフィン！
Surfing! Surfing!
ハイ！
High!
千夜伝心 海は今日も晴れ時々雪
Thousand-night transmission. The sea is also sunny with occasional snow today.
ココロによりパセ 前人未到の
More than my heart, an unprecedented
テルマイトで 窓ココも
With thermite, the window here too
あなたを待機中
Waiting for you
偶然だって必然のうち
Even coincidences are part of destiny
受信送信は見えない糸でしょ
Sending and receiving with an invisible thread, right?
三点こっちがしっくりくる
Three points, this way feels right
エンタースペースでエスケープ ザッポン
Escape into the enter space, splash!
ここは0と1の楽園
This is a paradise of 0s and 1s
ザッポン 広く深い世界から見つけ出して
Splash! Find me from this wide and deep world
エレクトリカル・サーフィン サーフィン
Electrical Surfing, Surfing
こちらに来て来て
Come here, come here
酸いも甘いも頂きます
I'll take the sour and the sweet
サーフィン サーフィン
Surfing, Surfing
手と手と手で拍手夢中目を開き明かしましょう
Hand in hand, applause, let's stay awake and obsess
攻略停止の海は今日も
The sea where strategy stops is today too
赤青緑でとにかく一杯一杯
Red, blue, and green, anyway, it's so full
悠々自適のテルマイトで
With free and easy thermite
間近のいつもの開始中
The usual starting is near
そんなこんなどんなもんだあんなよなこと
This and that, how is it, that kind of thing
下らなさこそが至福の時でしょ
Silliness is the ultimate bliss, right?
のんびりぐだらであららニコニコ
Relaxing, slacking off, oh my, smiling
コマンドデリートでリスボーン
Respawn with a delete command
ザッポン ここは雲の向こうの未来
Splash! This is the future beyond the clouds
ザッポン 全幕フライブライじゃじゃ物足りないの
Splash! Full curtain, fly by, just not enough
エレクトリカル・サーフィン サーフィン
Electrical Surfing, Surfing
こちらに来て来て
Come here, come here
酸いも甘いも忘れてさ
Forget the sour and the sweet
サーフィン サーフィン
Surfing, Surfing
手と手と手で拍手夢中にするわ覚えてて
Hand in hand, applause, I'll make you obsessed, remember it
サーフィン
Surfing
みんな サーフィン サーフィン
Everyone, Surfing, Surfing
サーフィン サーフィン
Surfing, Surfing
エレクトリカル・サーフィン サーフィン
Electrical Surfing, Surfing
こちらを見て見て
Look here, look here
空に輝く奇跡の輪
The miraculous ring shining in the sky
サーフィン サーフィン
Surfing, Surfing
手と手と手で鳴り止む夢中で
Hand in hand, the sound stops, in a trance
跳べ！ 跳べ！ 跳べ跳べ跳べ跳べ！
Jump! Jump! Jump, jump, jump, jump!
サーフィン サーフィン
Surfing, Surfing
こちらに来て来て
Come here, come here
酸いも甘いも頂きます
I'll take the sour and the sweet
サーフィン サーフィン
Surfing, Surfing
手と手と手で拍手夢中目を明かし明かしましょう
Hand in hand, applause, let's stay awake and obsess
はい！ というわけでサラマンダーと、エレクトリカル・サーフィンでした！
Yes! So that was Salamander and Electrical Surfing!
ノリノリな曲を最後に持ってきました！
I brought some upbeat songs at the end!
もう最後って言っても、まだあるんですけどね。
Even though I say "the end", there's still more to come.
さあ、そんな感じで、ここで、なんと！
Well, with that said, here, surprise!
告知が、グッズ告知があるとぉ！
There's an announcement, a merchandise announcement!
というわけで、グッズ告知を見ていきましょう。ドン！
So, let's take a look at the merchandise announcement. Bam!
ときのそら誕生日記念2023。
Tokino Sora Birthday Celebration 2023.
えー、誕生日記念フルセット、記念ボイス1種、
Um, Birthday Celebration Full Set, 1 type of commemorative voice,
記念グッズ3種が、ポップアップアクリルスタンド、
あん肝ぬいぐるみ、そらとおそろいキャップ、
3 types of commemorative goods: Pop-up Acrylic Stand,
Ankimo Plushie, and Sora-matching Cap,
そして誕生日記念フルセット購入特典は、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドです！
And the bonus for purchasing the Birthday Celebration Full Set is a hand-signed cheki-style bromide!
イェーイ！ イェー！ かわいい。本当ここ可愛いね。
Yay! Yay! Cute. It's really cute here.
はい、というわけで、詳しく見ていきましょうか。
Yes, so let's take a closer look.
はい、というわけで、まず1つ目はこちら。ポップアップアクリルスタンド。
Yes, so first of all, here it is. Pop-up Acrylic Stand.
こちらね、もちろんイラストおるだん先生に書いていただきました。
For this one, of course, the illustration was drawn by Ordan-sensei.
可愛いね。可愛いよね。そして、えー、もう、こういうポーズで。
It's cute. It's cute, isn't it? And, well, in this kind of pose.
あん肝もね、ここ、こんな感じにね、入れちゃってたりして。
Ankimo is also put in here like this.
あと、ぬんぬんもキラーンってしてたりして、とっても可愛いので、
ぜひぜひ注目してもらえると嬉しいです。
Also, Nunnun is sparkling, it's very cute,
so I'd be happy if you could check it out.
そして、続いてはこちら。あん肝ぬいぐるみ。
And next is this one. Ankimo Plushie.
めっちゃ大きいんですよね。大きいからこそ、私と同じようにね、あん肝をギュって、
It's really big. Because it's big, just like me, you can give Ankimo a big squeeze,
お部屋に置いてもらったり、まあね、あのー、一緒に、お出かけして、
keep it in your room, or, you know, go out together,
ぬいそらちゃんとあん肝でお出かけしてきた、みたいのも、
やってまらえたりするととっても嬉しいのかな、みたいな感じで思っております。
like "I went out with Nui-Sora-chan and Ankimo,"
if you could do that, I'd be very happy, I think.
めっちゃ可愛いぬいぐるみになったよ。嬉しい？
It turned out to be a really cute plushie. Are you happy?
嬉しいね。みんなのところにも行けるね。結構デカい。可愛いよね。
I'm happy. It can go to everyone's place too. It's quite big. It's cute, isn't it?
そして、続いてはこちら。そらとおそろいキャップ、
And next is this one. Sora-matching Cap,
ということで、今回私がつけているこのキャップと全く同じものですね。
so it's exactly the same as the cap I'm wearing this time.
あの、黒でみんなが使いやすいように、あとはね、ちょっと刺繍とかもね、
Um, it's black so it's easy for everyone to use, and also, the embroidery,
結構シンプルにしたので、普段使いからも、もう、できると思いますし、
I kept it quite simple, so I think you can use it for everyday use as well,
ライブの時とかにつけてきてもらってもとっても嬉しいなって思います。
and I'd be very happy if you wore it to concerts and things like that.
思います。
I think so too.
よろしくお願いします。キャップかわいいよね。私も、
Thank you. The cap is cute, isn't it? I'm,
めっちゃ嬉しかった、これ、キャップだーと思って。素敵やん。
also really happy with it, thinking "It's a cap!". It's lovely.
ありがとう。そして続いてが、こちら。
Thank you. And next up is this.
じゃあ、シチュエーションボイス「誕生日はきみと一緒に遊園地」
So, the situation voice "My birthday with you at the amusement park",
ということで、なんか、やっぱ、こういうね、
and well, you know, with this kind of,
元気な格好だったら遊園地行きたいでしょ？
energetic outfit, you'd want to go to an amusement park, right?
ということでね、遊園地のシチュエーションボイスにしました。
So I chose an amusement park situation for the voice track.
イェーイ。そしてこちら！
Yay. And this!
誕生日記念フルセットの方には特典で
The Birthday Celebration Full Set comes with a bonus
チェキ風ブロマイドカードも付いてきます。
Cheki-style bromide card as well.
こちらのチェキ風ブロマイドカードは、
This Cheki-style bromide card
直筆サイン入りのチェキ風ブロマイドカードとなっております。
will be hand-signed.
期間限定なので、みんな買えるから、今回。
It's for a limited time, so everyone can buy it this time.
だからぜひぜひ、期間限定、みんな、
So please, everyone, while it's available,
買いに行ってもらえると、私とっても
if you could go and buy it, I would be
嬉しいかなって思うよ。
really happy.
みんなの分、たくさんサイン書きますので、
I'll sign plenty for everyone,
よろしくお願いします！イェーイ！
so please look forward to it! Yay!
大丈夫、勝ち取りとかは、今回はないから！
Don't worry, there's no first-come, first-served battle this time!
だから、みんな、期間の間に買ってねー！
So, everyone, make sure to buy it during the period!
はい、というわけで、最後に歌を歌って終わりにしたいと思います。
All right then, I'd like to end by singing one last song.
もう最後の曲なんです。はやいね。
It's already the last song. That was fast.
さあ、よろしくお願いします。また、
Now then, please enjoy. Also,
あん肝が最終的に4人になってしまった。
there ended up being four Ankimos in the end.
や、後ろも合わせると、や、あの、真ん中のステージも合わせると、
No, if you count the ones in back... and on the center stage...
6！6！6人のあん肝が、はしゃいでる、はしゃいでるぞ。
Six! Six! Six Ankimos are frolicking around.
というわけで、え、今来たばっかり言ってくれて嬉しい。
Anyway, I'm glad some of you said you just arrived.
でも最後の曲になります。最後の曲盛り上がっていこう！
But it's time for the final song. Let's get fired up for it!
聴いてください、ベノム！
Please listen, Venom!
みんな今日は本当にありがとうございます！ハイ！
Thank you all so much for today! High!
あー足りないもの まだ僕らの人生
Ah, something's missing, in our lives still
正解どこなんだ 探せよ探せ
Where is the correct answer? Search for it, search
例外ない 二進も三進も 零下なら 劣化パレード
No exceptions, stuck either way, if it's below zero, it's a degradation parade
あー正味クソゲーだ カラカラの喉
Ah, it's basically a kusoge (crap game), a parched throat
あー携帯モード 興だ僕らの人生
Ah, mobile mode, it's our lives' fun
校内モード 狂だ 掲げよ掲げ
School mode, madness, hold it up, hold it up
成敗ない 吐き気も 殺意も 狭い台 売買生産
No punishment, nausea, murderous intent, a narrow stand, buying and selling production
あー後悔モード 狂だ 笑えよ笑え
Ah, regret mode, madness, laugh, laugh
心のレシピは かまってちょーだいジャンキー
The heart's recipe is a "Please pay attention to me" junkie
だんだん強がって 泥々に伏す
Gradually acting tough, collapsing into the mud
毒毒飲み込んで 苦しんで泣いて 逃げ出せないの ベノベノム サヨナラ
Swallowing poison, suffering and crying, I can't escape. Veno-Venom, goodbye.
あらま求愛性 孤独 毒流るる 相談な ねえ 最低の とんだ 存在価値
Oh my, courtship, loneliness, poison flows. Discuss it, hey, the worst, ridiculous existential value
独黒 こぼるる 愛 愛 叫べど ベノム ねえ
Single blackness spills out. Love, love, even if I scream, Venom, hey
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！最後ハイ！ハイ！
High! High! High! Last one, high! High!
あー最高点ゼロだ 僕らの人生
Ah, the highest point is zero, in our lives
断然テンションだ 掲げよ掲げ
Absolutely tension, hold it up, hold it up
抗えない てっぺん回って ロンリーなら 煩悩パレード
Can't resist, past the peak, if it's lonely, a desire parade
あーオーバードーズだ 揚がれよ揚がれ
Ah, it's an overdose, rise up, rise up
心の中身は 無理やり振りジャンキー
The heart's content is a forced-behavior junkie
どんどん強がって バラバラに伏す
Becoming more and more tough, collapsing into pieces
毒毒飲み込んで 苦しんで泣いて 逃げ出せないの ベノベノム
Swallowing poison, suffering and crying, I can't escape. Veno-Venom
あらま求愛性 孤独 毒流るる 相談な ねえ 最低の とんだ 存在価値
Oh my, courtship, loneliness, poison flows. Discuss it, hey, the worst, ridiculous existential value
欲しがるる 愛 愛 叫べど ベノム ねえ
Desiring, love, love, even if I scream, Venom, hey
惑わせ 毒々 回るる 障害な ねえ 最低の しくしく 存在価値
Perplexing, poison-poison, spinning. An obstacle, hey, the worst, sobbing existential value
お粗末 ろくろく 消えぬる 愛 愛 ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Poor quality, barely, disappearing. Love, love. High! High! High! High!
求愛性 孤独 毒流るる 相談な ねえ 最低の とんだ 存在価値
Courtship, loneliness, poison flows. Discuss it, hey, the worst, ridiculous existential value
独黒 こぼるる 愛 愛 叫べど ベノム
Single blackness spills out. Love, love, even if I scream, Venom
叫べど ベノム 叫べど ベノム ねえ
Even if I scream, Venom. Even if I scream, Venom, hey
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
High! High! High!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
今日は！本当に！ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you all so much for today!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
またねー！
See you later!
ときのそら 生誕祭ライブ 2023
新衣装お披露目
Tokino Sora Birthday Live 2023
New Outfit Reveal